Guide to the Washington Square Park (New York, N.Y.) and Washington Square Area Image Collection, 1850-1990 NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001
New York University Archives
- Series III: University Building, 1832-1894, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1836, Elevation and Plan by Town, Davis, Dakin & Douglas. Diary Excerpts, A.J. Davis (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - University Building, Exterior elevation and building plan, 1836; CB_UB_1_6_01; negative print, 8 x 10 inches. Image is of exterior elevation and building plan.; Town Davis Dakin Douglas. Architects. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - University Building, Exterior elevation and building plan, 1836; CB_UB_1_6_02; black-and-white print (photocopy) 8 x 10 inches of engraving (print); Town Davis Dakin Douglas. Architects. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1837-1930s, Views from University Publications & Printed Materials, circa 1837-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1837 July 20; CB_UB_1_7_01; black-and-white negative, 3 x 4 inches. Image is of illustration, reprinted in rural repository (1846) and Mason's Discourse (1847) (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - University Building, Exterior, circa 1936; CB_UB_1_7_02; Engraving, 2.5 x 1.75 inches. Image is from flyer (printed matter): "New York Univeristy presented by The Society for the Libraries." (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1935; CB_UB_1_7_03; illustration, 3.5 x 4.5 inches. Image is from an invitation pamphlet: "New York Univeristy Council Dinner, Tuesday, June Eleventh, Nineteen Thirty-five, The Waldorf-Astoria, New York." (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 3)
    - University Building, Exterior, probably 1848; CB_UB_1_7_04; illustration, 3.75 x 5.75 inches. Image is from page in unidentified publication (page with title: "Pictorial Library of Useful Information," p. 409). (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 4)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1835; CB_UB_1_7_05; black-and-white print, 3 x 4 inches of engraving. Image is of a montage of photographs. (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 5)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1861-1863; CB_UB_1_7_06; Engraving, 4.25 x 5 inches. Image is from catalog (1861-1862) frontispiece. (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 6)
    - University Building, Partial Exterior, 1934; CB_UB_1_7_07; Engraving, 3.125 x 3.625 inches. Image is from publication: The Album, 1934, p. 25. (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 7)
    - University Building, Exterior, circa 1896; CB_UB_1_7_08; Engraving (enlarged), 5 x 4 inches. Image is from publication: Lamb, Martha J., and Mrs. Burton Harrison. History of the City of New York: Its Origin Rise, and Progress. Volume 3. New York: A.S. Barnes, 1896, p. 719. Artist and engraver unspecified, although artists and engravers whose works appear in the volume are listed on page xi. (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 8)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1844, Valentine's Manual View (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1844; CB_UB_1_8_01; Illustration, 4.5 x 3.125 inches. Image is from publication: Valentine's Manual, 1844. (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 1)
      Not for Reproduction: Property of Metropolitan Museum of Art.
  - University Building - Exterior, 1846, Rural Repository (Same as commencement ticket, 1837) View (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1846; CB_UB_1_9_01; Engraving, 4.5 x 2.5 inches. Image is from publication: Rural Repository, June 20, 1846, Vol. 22, Number 21, p. 1. (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1847, View From Discourse... by C. Mason (Same as Rural Repository, 1846) (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1847; CB_UB_1_10_01; Engraving, 4 x 3.125 inches. Image is from publication: C. Mason, The Growth--University City of New York, a Discourse... (Box 1, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1848, Pictorial Library of Useful Information, Vol 2, Number 10 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1848; CB_UB_1_11_01; Engraving, 2 x 4. Image is from publication: Pictorial Library of Useful Information, 1848?. (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1850, Hoff View, Illustration, 7.5 x 6 inches. Hoff View. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1850; CB_UB_1_12_01; Black-and-white (print), 4 x 6 inches, engraving. Hoff view. (Box 1, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, c. 1850, Howland/Anstice View, ca. 1850 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - University Building, Exterior, ca. 1850; CB_UB_1_13_01; Engraving, 4.5 x. 2 inches. Image is from publication: The Old University Building and the Societys' Years on Washington Square in New-York Historical Society Quarterly, July 1948.; Howland, William (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Univeristy Building - Exterior, c. 1850, Richardson and Cox Engraving, Illustration, 7.5 x 8.25 inches. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1853; CB_UB_1_14_01; Black-and-white print, 7.5 x 8.5 inches of engraving (print). (Box 1, Folder 14, Item 1)
      Do Not Reproduce - Copyright for image is unclear.
      New York University |x Buildings.; Richardson & Cox.; Washington Square Park (New York, N.Y.)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1851, Boetticher View/ Parade Grounds (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1851; CB_UB_1_15_01; Illustration, 9.5 x 6.38 inches. (Box 1, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1852, Wade View (Printed in Gleason's Pictorial, September 4, 1852) (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1852; CB_UB_1_16_01; Engraving, 10 x 7.75 inches. Image in publication: Gleason's Pictorial, September 4, 1852. (Box 1, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1867, View from Manual of the Corporation/ New York Public Library (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1867; CB_UB_2_1_01; Engraving, 3.25 x 4 inches. Image is from page in Manual of the Corporation/New York Public Library (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, c. 1867, Photograph (Front Elevation), ca. 1867 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - University Building, Exterior, ca.1867; CB_UB_2_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.75 x 6 inches. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1870?, Milgram Donation (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1870?; CB_UB_2_3_01; black-and-white (photograph), 4.5 x 6 inches. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1878, Hunter Rendering (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1878; CB_UB_2_4_01; Engraving, 8 x 12 inches.; Hunter, Frederick Leo, 1858-1943 (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, c. 1880, Snow Scene, ca. 1880 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - University Building, Exterior, ca. 1880; CB_UB_2_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.5 x 10.5 inches. (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - University Building, Partial Exterior, ca. 1880; CB_UB_2_5_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.5 x 9.5 inches. (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - University Building - Exterior, c. 1890, Photograph (Museum of the City of New York), ca. 1890 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - University Building, Exterior, ca. 1890; CB_UB_2_6_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 6.875 x 9.375 inches. (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 1)
      Do Not Reproduce - Property of Museum of the City of New York (MCNY)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1890, McKim, Mead, White, University Building renovation plans - transparencies, negatives, and prints (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - University Building, Exterior Elevation and Building Plan (negatives), 1890; CB_UB_2_7_01; Color negative print, 8.5 x 10 inches. Image is of basement building plan. (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - University Building, Building Renovation Plan, 1890; CB_UB_2_7_02; Color illustration, 7.5 x 10.5 inches. Image is of second floor plan. (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 2)
      Negatives.; New York University |x Buildings.
    - University Building, Building Renovation Plan, 1890; CB_UB_2_7_03; Color illustration, 7.375 x 10.375 inches. Image is of second floor building renovation plan. (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 3)
    - University Building, Building Renovation Plan, 1890; CB_UB_2_7_04; Color Negative print 8.5 x 10 inches. Image is of third floor renovation plans. (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 4)
    - University Building, Building Renovation Plan, 1890; CB_UB_2_7_05 (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 5)
    - University Building, Building Renovation Plan, 1890; CB_UB_2_7_06 (Box 2, Folder 7, Item 6)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1890, Photograph (Front Elevation with Park Benches) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1893?-1894; CB_UB_3_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - University Building, Exterior view looking east, undated; CB_UB_3_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 7 x 8.75 inches. (Box 3, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1891, "Number Five" (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1891; CB_UB_3_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.575 x 7.575 inches. From back "Number 5 is a front view of the University Building taken in 1891. It is the finest photograph ever taken of the old structure." (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1891, View with Asbury Methodist Church (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1891; CB_UB_3_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.25 x 6.75 inches. Image is from Asbury Methodist Church across Washington Square Park. (Box 3, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1892, "421" (in lower left corner of image) (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1892; CB_UB_3_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.5 x 9.5 inches. (Box 3, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1892 Negative 4/1142 (Partial View) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1892; CB_UB_3_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.5 x 9.5 inches. Image is partial view of the west wing of the building. (Box 3, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1892 or 1893 Roof of South Wing - Photo taken by Dr. D.W. Hering, 1892? 1893? (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - University Building, Exterior Roof of South Wing, 1892-1893?; CB_UB_3_6_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5.875 x 8.575 inches. View of South Wing Roof.; D.W. (Daniel Webster) Hering, 1850-1938 (Box 3, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1893 Snow Scene (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1893; CB_UB_3_7_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.25 x 9.5 inches. (Box 3, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1893? (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1893?; CB_UB_3_8_01; Negative print, 4 x 4.75 inches. Image is a view looking east with a horse and carriage. (Box 3, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1893? "Richard Original" (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1893?; CB_UB_3_9_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7 x 8.75 inches. (Box 3, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1894 Snow Scene (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1894; CB_UB_3_10_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.575 x 9.5 inches. (Box 3, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1894? Tower (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - University Building, Exterior, Cecil Dreeme Tower, 1894?; CB_UB_3_11_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.5 x 8.5 inches. (Box 3, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior 19th Century, Harris, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - University Building, Exterior, undated; CB_UB_3_12_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.25 x 7.5 inches.; Harris, Luther (Box 3, Folder 12, Item 1)
    - University Building, Exterior, undated; CB_UB_3_12_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8.25 x 7.75 inches.; Harris, Luther (Box 3, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - University Building - Exterior, undated Montages, N.D. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - University Building, Exterior, undated; CB_UB_3_13_01; Illustration, 5.5 x 9.5 inches. Image is a montage of smaller illustrations of University Building and Washington Square Park. (Box 3, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - University Building - Exterior, 1894? (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1894?; CB_UB_3_16_01; Illustration, 6.5 x 9 inches. Image is a watercolor of Alfred Zucker's University Building.; Welch, G.; Zucker, Alfred, 1852- (Box 3, Folder 16, Item 1)
    - University Building, Exterior, 1894?; CB_UB_3_16_02; Illustration, 7.25 x 8.25 inches. Image is a watercolor by G. Welch of Alfred Zucker's University Building.; Welch, G.; Zucker, Alfred, 1852- (Box 3, Folder 16, Item 2)
  - University Building - Interior, Chancellor's Office, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - University Building, Interior - Chancellor's Room, 1892; CB_UB_4_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.75 x 6.75 inches. Image is of chancellor's room. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 1)
      MacCracken, Henry Mitchell, 1840-1918; New York University |x Buildings.
    - University Building, Interior - Chancellor's Room, 1892; CB_UB_4_1_02; Illustration, 7.25 x 9.5 inches. Image is from the publication Frank Leslie's Montly, March 1892. (Box 4, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - University Building - Interior, 1850-1892, Chapel (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, undated; CB_UB_4_2_01; Illustration 7.5 x 5.25 inches. Image is from unknown publication p. 60. (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, undated; CB_UB_4_2_02; Illustration, 8.5 x 7.375 inches. (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 2)
      Do Not Reproduce - Property of New-York Historical Society (N-YHS).
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, 1856; CB_UB_4_2_03; Illustration, 7.5 x 8.375 inches. (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, 1850; CB_UB_4_2_04; Illustration, 4.5 x 5.575 inches. (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 4)
      Bancroft, George, 1800-1891; Bethune, George W.; Betts, Samuel Rossiter, 1786-1868; Brodhead, John Romeyn, 1814-1873; Bronson, Greene Carrier, 1789-1863; Bryant, William Cullen, 1794-1878; Calhoun, John Caldwell, 1782-1850; Campbell, William W., 1806-1881; Cass, Lewis, 1782-1866; Clay, Henry, 1777-1852; Crittenden, John Jordan, 1786-1863; de Peyster, Frederick; de Witt, Thomas; Dix, John A., (John Adams), 1798-1879; Duer, John, 1782-1858; Edmonds, John W.; Edward Everett, 1794-1865; Fillmore, Millard, 1800-1874; Fish, Hamilton, 1808-1893; Hall, Nathan Kelsey, 1810-1874; Hawks, Francis L., (Francis Lister), 1798-1866; Hoffman, Ogden, 1793-1856; Hunt, Washington, 1811-1867; John Ellis Wool, 1784-1869; Lord, Daniel; Luther Bradish, 1783-1863; Marcy, William Learned, 1786-1857; Martin Van Buren, 1782-1862; McKeon, John, 1808-1883; Morris, Robert Hunter, 1808-1855; Mott, Valentine, 1785-1865; Nelson, Samuel; Oakley, Thomas Jackson, 1783-1857; Pierce, Franklin, 1804-1869; Pratt, Zadock, 1790-1871; Robinson, Edward, 1794-1863; Scott, Winfield, 1786-1866; Seymour, Horatio, 1810-1866; Stevens, Alexander H., (Alexander Hodgdon), 1789-1869; Steward, William H.; Taylor, Thomas H.; Tuckerman, Henry T., (Henry Theodore), 1813-1871; Van Buren, John, 1810-1866; Wainwright, Jonathan Mayhew, 1792-1854; Walker, Robert John, 1801-1869; Webster, Daniel, 1785-1852; Wood, George; New York University |x Buildings.
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, 1850; CB-UB_4_2_05; Illustration, 6 x 8.75 inches. (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 5)
      Bancroft, George, 1800-1891; Bethune, George W.; Betts, Samuel Rossiter, 1786-1868; Brodhead, John Romeyn, 1814-1873; Bronson, Greene Carrier, 1789-1863; Bryant, William Cullen, 1794-1878; Calhoun, John Caldwell, 1782-1850; Campbell, William W., 1806-1881; Cass, Lewis, 1782-1866; Clay, Henry, 1777-1852; Crittenden, John Jordan, 1786-1863; de Peyster, Frederick; de Witt, Thomas; Dix, John A., (John Adams), 1798-1879; Duer, John, 1782-1858; Edmonds, John W.; Fillmore, Millard, 1800-1874; Fish, Hamilton, 1808-1893; Hall, Nathan Kelsey, 1810-1874; Hawks, Francis L., (Francis Lister), 1798-1866; Hoffman, Ogden, 1793-1856; Hunt, Washington, 1811-1867; John Ellis Wool, 1784-1869; Lord, Daniel; Marcy, William Learned, 1786-1857; Martin Van Buren, 1782-1862; McKeon, John, 1808-1883; Morris, Robert Hunter, 1808-1855; Mott, Valentine, 1785-1865; Nelson, Samuel; Oakley, Thomas Jackson, 1783-1857; Pierce, Franklin, 1804-1869; Pratt, Zadock, 1790-1871; Robinson, Edward, 1794-1863; Scott, Winfield, 1786-1866; Seymour, Horatio, 1810-1866; Stevens, Alexander H., (Alexander Hodgdon), 1789-1869; Taylor, Thomas H.; Van Buren, John, 1810-1866; Wainwright, Jonathan Mayhew, 1792-1854; Walker, Robert John, 1801-1869; Webster, Daniel, 1785-1852; Wood, George; New York University |x Buildings.
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, 1892; CB_UB_4_2_06; Illustration, 6 x 9.5 inches. Image is from Frank Leslie's Monthly, March 1892. (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - University Building, Interior - Chapel, 1894; CB_UB_4_2_07; Black-and-white print (photograph), 4.575 x 6.75 inches. (Box 4, Folder 2, Item 7)
  - University Building - Interior, Chemistry Lab, ca. 1893 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - University Building, Interior - Chemistry Lab, 1895; CB_UB_4_3_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 4, Folder 3, Item 1)
      Chemistry.; New York University |x Buildings.
  - University Building - Interior, Council Room, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - University Building, Interior - Council Room, 1894; CB_UB_4_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 7.5 x 9.5 inches. (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - University Building, Interior - Council Room, 1894; CB_UB_4_4_02; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 4, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - University Building - Interior, Eucleian Hall, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - University Building, Interior - Eucleian Hall, 1894; CB_UB_4_5_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 4, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - University Building - Interior, Greek Room, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - University Building, Interior - Greek Hall, 1894; CB_UB_4_6_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 4, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - University Building - Interior, Hennessy's Studio, 1866 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - University Building, Interior - Hennessy's Studio, 1866; CB_UB_4_7_01; Illustration, 3.5 x 3.75 inches. Image is from publication "New York University 1832: 1932" by Theodore F. Jones, 1933.; Jones, Theodore Francis, 1885- (Box 4, Folder 7, Item 1)
      Hennessy, William John, 1839-1917; New York University |x Buildings.
  - University Building - Interior, Junior Law Room, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - University Building, Interior - Junior Law Room, 1894; CB_UB_4_8_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 4, Folder 8, Item 1)
      New York University |x Buildings.; New York University. School of Law.
  - University Building - Interior, Library, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - University Building, Interior - Library, 1894; CB_UB_5_1_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 1)
      New York University |x Buildings.; New York University. Libraries.
  - University Building - Interior, Pedagogy Office, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - University Building, Interior - Pedagogy Office, 1894; CB_UB_5_2_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 1)
      New York University |x Buildings.; Pedagogy.
  - University Building - Interior, Philomathean Hall, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - University Building, Interior - Philomathean Hall, 1894; CB_UB_5_3_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - University Building - Interior, Physics Lab, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - University Building, Interior - Physics Lab, 1894; CB_UB_5_4_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 4.5 x 6 inches. (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 1)
      New York University |x Buildings.; Physics |x Study and teaching |y 19th century.
    - University Building, Interior - Physics Lab, 1894; CB_UB_5_4_02; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - University Building - Interior, Plans, 1830s (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - University Building, Interior - Plans, undated; CB_UB_5_5_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5.75 x 9 inches. Image is of northwest corner room building plan and interior elevation.; Davis, Alexander Jackson (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 1)
      Do Not Reproduce - Property of the Metropolitan Museum of Art.
      Blueprints.; New York University |x Buildings.
    - University Building, Interior - Plans, 1832; CB_UB_5_5_02; negative print, 4 x 4.75 inches. Image is of exterior elevation and building plan of a drawing from Alexander Jackson Davis's diary.; Davis, Alexander Jackson (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - University Building, Interior - Plans, undated; CB_UB_5_5_03; Black-and-white print (photograph), 6.75 x 8 inches. Image is of Chapel floor plan by Alexander Jackson Davis.; Davis, Alexander Jackson (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - University Building - Interior, Richards' Studio, 1894? (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - University Building, Interior - Richards' Studio, 1894?; CB_UB_5_6_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 8.5 x 10 inches. (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - University Building - Interior, Small Chapel, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - University Building, Interior - Small Chapel, 1894; CB_UB_5_7_01; Black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches. (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 1)
- Series IV: Washington Square Campus Buildings
  - Alumni Hall - Exteriors, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5580; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5583; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5585; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5587; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5889; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Pelaez, Jose (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5591; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Pelaez, Jose (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5594; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5597; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Pelaez, Jose (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5600; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5602; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Alumni Hall, circa 1990; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5604; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 1, Folder 1, Item 11)
  - Alumni Hall - Interiors (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Interior of Alumni Hall, Looking South on 3rd Avenue, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5607; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - ANTA Theater, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - ANTA Theater, Looking South, 1968; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5611; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 1)
      New York University |x Buildings.; Theater.
    - ANTA Theater, 1964; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5613; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches; Pellettieri, Luigi (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - ANTA Theater, Looking South-West, 1968; NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001_ref5615; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 3)